Monsters of Man is a science fiction, action film directed by Mark Toia.
A robotics company vying to win a lucrative military contract team up with
a corrupt CIA agent to conduct an illegal live field test.
They deploy four weaponized prototype robots into a suspected drug manufacturing camp in the
Golden Triangle, assuming they'd be killing drug runners that no one would miss.
Six doctors on a humanitarian mission witness the
brutal slaughter and become prime targets.
Major, played by Neal McDonough.
Mason, played by Brett Tutor.
Boller, played by Jose Rosete.
Kroger, played by David Haverty.
Jordan, played by Paul Haapaniemi.
Jantz, played by Ryan Hough.
Monsters of Man is an Australian science fiction indie film written and directed by Australian cinematographer and director Mark Toia about a robotics team testing
a new military robot for the CIA in the Golden triangle hunting drug traffickers that becomes sentient and goes rogue, attacking nearby villagers.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.